https://www.fedprobrands.com/privacy-policy

Menu
Search
FedPro
Search:
Search
Menu
Products Pipe Thread SealantsPTFE TapesGasket MakersPenetrantsLubricantsGauging PasteMarking PaintCleanersAccessoriesVisit Thred TaperVisit EverSEALGasoila Catalog PDFDistributorsSupport Artwork LogosProduct ArtworkGuides & Charts Sealant Application GuideQuick & Easy Sealant Reference GuidePTFE Tape Specifications
CATALOG
Download Catalog PDF (2.3mb)
Catálogo Español PDF (1.2mb)
MSDS/SDSAboutContact
Home
FedPro Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
Categories
ProductsPipe Thread SealantsPTFE TapesGasket MakersPenetrantsLubricantsGauging PasteMarking PaintCleanersAccessoriesVisit Thred TaperVisit EverSEALGasoila Catalog PDFDistributorsSupportArtworkLogosProduct ArtworkGuides & ChartsSealant Application GuideQuick & Easy Sealant Reference GuidePTFE Tape SpecificationsMSDS/SDSAboutContact
Site Map
Terms of Use
Privacy Policy
Products
Distributors
Support
MSDS
About
© 2020 FedPro. All Rights Reserved.
